(Sheldon:)Trust me, Kripke will fall easy prey
to my psychological warfare. Observe.
(Leonard:)Kripke.
(Sheldon:)I would ask if your robot
is prepared to meet its maker...
(Sheldon:)...but as you are its maker,
clearly the two of you have met.
What is his problem?
(Raj:)Way to bust out
the Jedi mind tricks, dude.
I wanna make sure that
we're all clear.
(Leonard:)Standard Robotic
Fighting League rules apply.
Are you crazy?
This is a street fight.
The street has no rules.
(Sheldon:)He's right, Leonard.
The paradigm is to the death.
(Kripke:)I will, however, give you the opportunity
to concede my superiority now...
...and offer me your robot
as the spoils of war.
(Sheldon:)Never. I'd rather see Monte dead
than in your hands.
That could be easily arranged.
Ready, set, go?
(Leonard:)- Do it.
- All right, then.